ansaluniversity.edu.in 2016-11-26

# Privacy Policy | Home

You may visit Ansal University (AU) website without revealing any personal information wherever permissible. Certain transactions such as Name, email-id and Phone no. may require submission of personal information like profile updates and certain databases. Ansal University will not disclose to any third party any personal information for commercial purpose and such information will be utilized only for the intended purpose if required by law, court order, statutory bodies, rules & regulations or for improving our website or for the security of our network or for any purpose as deemed necessary.

Ansal University may disclose such information to our employees and other concerned having a genuine need to know the information.

Ansal University’s web server may record the IP address of the computer, information about the browser and Operating System you are using, date and time of access and page which directs you to Ansal University website. This information may be used to monitor and improve AU website and to generate statistical reports on website traffic. We may also use cookies to track session information and/or to deliver services and/or for any other purpose of website.

While we put our best efforts to protect the privacy of users, however, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information shared with us and you do so at your own risk.

This privacy policy may be revised/modified/amended at any point of time at the sole discretion of the University.
